Broke up with Luna. Freeze it out! That electric sword of yours is useless! The damage is so low! Do you have my ice cow?
I am Haotian, and here I am the strongest Ice King, who can freeze people to death without revealing his body. N-two.
Many people subconsciously think that N-two only has control but no damage, and cannot replace operators with damage attributes at all.
It is even more impossible to use them to kill singles and three people randomly. Today, the main package will directly teach you N-two’s top skipping and crushing style with three moves.
1. Attack combo, first throw the tracking shock egg and explore the point mark.
Then throw cold cans at the enemy's only way to seal the road and add low temperature. If the enemy is trapped, he can easily take it away with his gun.
It doesn't matter if your marksmanship is not good here, it's hard to fight back when the opponent is frozen. Of course,
If you know the opponent's location, you can also throw a cold can into the target range first. The range of the cold can is very large.
Hits are not an issue. Then press forward and throw shock bombs to lock the target. At this time,
The opponent was spraying medicine because of the freezing skill, so he directly pressed forward to grab the ginseng belt. Second, defensive combos,
Place a cold can on the road that must be passed on the opposite side, so that the opposite side does not dare to force it. After that, the shock probe exposes the position and locks the trend.
After the enemy is trapped, he has no choice but to change positions to avoid freezing to death in place. At this time, we will just fight it out.
Take away with ease. Three major cheating techniques: The ultimate move in night combat requires firing six grenades in thirty seconds.
Many players continue to shoot continuously as soon as the ultimate move is activated, fearing that the ultimate move will not be effective when the time is up.
However, the actual measurement of the main package found that the effect is directly doubled when the grenade is inserted into the gun.
In this wave, the three people on the opposite side gathered together to attack, preparing to attack. The main package relies on the staircase terrain to start pulling.
First, a rebound howitzer suppresses the opponent's front.
When you see the enemy walking upwards, avoid freezing damage, kill them immediately with a shot, and follow the trend upwards.
And fired another grenade into the gap. Suppress enemies who want to replenish their guns and get frozen feedback.
Directly cut the gun and grab it at close range. Finally, cut back to the howitzer to finish, one rebounded,
One predicts the output to the gap in the stairs, and finally grabs the third passive remaining health one. This wave didn’t even drop armor.
One against three, the team will be wiped out. Hey, don't tell me that this hero is really fun. He can skillfully use the three combos in the main package.
The liquid bullets moved directly across the sky.
get out of class is over.